Harvey: I just don't understand.
Louis: There's a lot of things that you
don't understand, especially...
Everyone is wearing a black tie.
And you're wearing a gray tie.
This is acceptable
at a black tie affair.
There's nothing wrong
with the tie that I'm wearing.
Thank you.
- Would you like a glass?
- Yes, please.
Champagne, sir?
Is it? From the region.
In France.
Because if it's not,
it's called sparkling wine.
And I don't really
drink sparkling wine.
Forget it.
Forgive him. His parents
really wanted a girl. Never got over it.
Louis: Wait a minute, you can taste
the difference.
I'm not being a snob.
Not a snob? You sound
like frasier's brother.
Niles crane was
completely misunderstood.
Jessica: Okay, boys.
You don't want me to
give you a time out, now do you?
I'd be willing to stand in a corner,
if you agree to paddle his bottom.
Louis: Oh, that's hilarious.
I'm just saying, that if
they want us to donate to their charity,
they might as well step it up.
You know, make me want
to give away my money.
Your money? You're here representing
the firm, Louis.
And we've always been committed to
giving back to the community.
Jessica. Is that...
Tori, yes. And I owe her a call.
Excuse me.
Do I smell like sausage?
No more than usual. Why?
Uh, because I'm about to meet the future
Mrs. Louis litt.
I had pizza before I came,
and I just want to make sure I still am
not emanating any aroma.
Oh, you're emanating something.
It's called pheromones. And women find
it irresistible.
Watch.
Jessica: Harvey.
You remember Tori?
Of course. Nice to see you.
I told Jessica,
I don't really want to talk shop when
we're here to support a good cause.
Well, that's the beautiful
thing about a retainer.
We're always on call
when you need us.
So, how can we help?
It involves one of our
most trusted senior vps.
Something recently came to light about
his past. I'm shocked by it, really.
Tell us where it hurts
and we'll make it go away.
Oh. Oh.
Wait. Wait.
- Wait?
- Ah. Yeah. Let's just...
This feels like
it's moving really fast.
I should slow down?
No. I just... I mean, like...
I just got out of a relationship.
And...
- Right.
- You kind of did, too.
I wasn't really seeing anyone.
You know what I mean.
Trevor.
- Yeah. Trevor.
- That's right. Trevor.
- Uh.
Yeah. No, you're right.
We should slow down.
- I should make us some tea.
- Mmm.
- You want some tea?
- Yeah.
Yeah, let's drink some tea.
What's the, uh, Harvard club?
Oh. It's a... it's, like, this clubhouse
for Harvard alumni.
Yeah, that invite is, uh...
It's for this networking
thing for lawyers. I got it at work.
Hmm. Would you go?
Wait, are you kidding me?
No. I have a hard enough time
pretending at work.
It's not like I want
to enter the lion's den.
Well, if you were gonna go
and you were going
to take a date...
It would be you.
I'd love to take you.
Uh-oh. Uh-oh.
Who's moving too fast now?
Oh, I'll do it.
Saying all the right things.
Mmm.
Mike: Hey. What's the emergency?
Couldn't find
a date to the prom?
We're firing Stan Jacobson.
Who?
Senior vice president,
dreibach accounting.
- Our accounting firm?
- Yes.
They're our firm and our client.
How's that possible?
They signed a conflict
of interest waiver.
Look at that. He's actually learning
how the law works.
Acquaint yourself with dreibach's
company charter
and Stan's original
employment contract.
- What did he do?
- He lied.
He lied? About what? Wait. Let me guess.
He cooked the books.
God, doesn't anyone on wall street put
in an honest day's work anymore?
Actually, he's got a stellar record
as a senior vp.
He lied on his resume.
Never got a cpa license, never even went
to business school.
He lied about where
he went to school,
and now he's getting fired?
Dreibach does the books
for half of wall street.
Word gets out that
a senior staff is a fraud,
they're going to start
bleeding clients.
We have to do this fast
and keep it quiet.
Relax. That's not
going to happen to you.
But I would get fired
if Jessica found out.
Found out what?
Just told me he's a virgin.
That doesn't
surprise me one bit.
All in due time, Mike.
You have those severance quotes?
See the money wanna stay
for your meal
get another piece of pie
for your wife
everybody wanna know how it feel
everybody wanna see
what it's like
I'll even eat a bean pie
I don't mind
me and missy is so early
busy, busy making money
all right!
All step back I'm 'bout to dance
the greenback boogie
Guard:
Oh. Where you headed, doll?
Jenny: Pearson hardman,
to see Mike Ross.
Guard: Uh. He expecting you?
No, I just was going to
drop this off.
No appointment,
I can't let you up.
Do I look like a terrorist?
Do I look like I want
to lose my job?
Rachel: Jenny?
- Rachel.
- Hey. You here to see Mike?
Sort of. I just... I was going to drop
this suit off for him.
Harvey called late last night.
Some big emergency.
And Mike ended up
staying the night.
Actually, could you help me out?
I am running so late to work.
- Sure.
- Oh, my god. Thank you.
Thanks.
- Okay.
- Thank you.
Oh! And can you tell Mike that I left
the key under the mat?
Absolutely.
- Thank you so much, Rachel.
- You're welcome.
You're amazing.
I'm up. I'm up.
Your girlfriend stopped by.
Dropped that off for you.
Girlfriend?
Did you guys move in
together already?
What? No, we... she's not my...
- Why do you care?
- Idon1.
What... what was
the big emergency last night?
Um... Harvey.
He's firing some big vp from our
accounting firm this morning.
Stan Jacobson?
Yeah. Why? You know him?
No, he was just checking in at reception
when I got there.
Oh, my god. I gotta change.
I will let him know
that you'll be right there?
- Thanks.
- Mmmhmm.
Mike: Performance numbers,
hr guidelines, severance quotes,
and Stan's in the waiting room.
Did you sleep here last night?
I wouldn't exactly
call it sleeping.
- Where did you get that suit?
- Uh, Rachel.
No, I mean, Jenny gave it to Rachel
downstairs.
She slept over last night.
Jenny did. Not Rachel.
Do I really need to be here
when you fire this guy?
You want to learn
how it's done, right?
I read this guy's employment records,
Harvey. He's smart, talented, loyal...
Aw, and you feel bad
for him. I'm shocked.
Where's my smoking gun?
The background check that confirmed Stan
lied about his credentials.
It never came through.
On it.
Come in. Come in.
Um, could you help me
with something?
I need to get this fax
for Harvey, and...
Good morning.
Good morning. He needs a...
You can tell, can't you?
I bet you everybody can.
Tell what?
You waxed your eyebrows?
I was with the most
beautiful woman last night.
Um, she waxed your eyebrows?
We did a lot of things
last night,
and waxing wasn't one of them,
if you know what I mean.
Oh, god. Uh. Well, that's great.
I'm here to ask...
Her name's charisse, and we have
so much in common.
And Mike, there was like this...
There was like this... mmm.
- Mmm-mmm.
- You know, like...
- Lmea"mmm.
- Mmm.
Like a chemical thing that would happen
when our bodies would touch.
No, I really don't want to have this
conversation with you.
Oh, come on.
We're both guys. Right?
Little locker room
talk around the office?
I mean, that creates
a little male bonding.
Yeah. That's crazy, I just heard my
name. Did you hear that?
Someone's calling.
I'm gonnajust...
One second, okay?
He's probably still a virgin.
Mr. Jacobson.
Hi. Mike Ross,
Harvey's associate.
So sorry to keep you waiting.
It's just going to be a couple more
minutes, okay? Okay, great. Thank you.
Yes, I hear you. Your office couldn't
find a copy.
Can you tell me the name
of the security firm you guys used
to do the background check?
Okay, great. Uh, nope, that's great.
I found the number myself.
Thank you.
Sally. Yes, this is Mike Ross
from Pearson hardman.
I'm calling regarding
a background check you guys did...
Uh, sure.
You could refuse to cooperate.
But then, you would be wrong.
Uh, Sally, hold on one minute?
Yeah. Uh, no. Stan is going
to be there in two minutes.
He's in the bathroom. Okay.
Sally, you there?
Let's do this. Uh...
I'm going to fax you the subpoena that
I'm holding in my hand right now,
and you can show that
to your boss and then we...
Great. Uh, let me send you
my fax number now.
Yes.
Stan.
Oh! Hey. We ready?
Yes. I'm sorry about that.
No worries.
I know you, by the way.
7-6-1 -1 -0-5-3.
Your employee code.
- See, I remember everyone that way.
- Ah.
Anyway, you are taking me
to see Harvey.
I have been dying to meet him.
- Why is that?
- His balls.
His autographed ones?
I'm a huge baseball fan.
Oh! Right. Really?
Oh, yeah, yeah.
No, if I wasn't an accountant,
I would be a major league scout.
I can tell you anything
you want to know
- just by looking at somebody's numbers.
- Huh.
For instance, slugging percentage
versus strike-outs
- during spring training...
- Do you...
Do you want to walk and talk?
Maybe?
Ah. See, the thing is,
it's usually what we call
in the trade a miscorrelation.
Stan Jacobson...
Mr. Specter, it is a pleasure.
Stan, it's nice to meet you.
Has Mike...
Oh, my god. Oh, my god.
Is that them?
0h!
Jeter. Hank Aaron.
No way. Maris?
That's not number 61, is it?
No, but it was
signed by Tracy...
Stan: Stallard.
Big baseball fan.
Stan, why don't you have
a seat over here?
Why don't I, uh,
get us some waters?
Stan: Sorry. I get talking about
baseball, I cannot stop.
Well, I know how
valuable your time is.
I do do the books.
And speaking of which,
your assistant tells me
you wanted to go over something from
your last audit.
I could really use a water.
Stan, we're not here to go over any
accounting business.
You're here because
you're being let go.
What?
Harvey: It's not going to feel as
surprising when you understand why.
The firm looked
into your background recently.
They know you lied
about passing the cpa exam.
You were hired because of your
outstanding credentials
and the reality is,
they never existed.
I've been there for nine years.
My work has been nothing but...
I mean, why would this
even matter now?
You've been committing fraud your entire
career. The liability it presents...
No, I don't accept this.
Take a deep breath. Once you go over
the severance numbers,
you'll see that we've been
more than fair.
Fair.
You think this is fair?
We understand how difficult this must
be, Stan. How you must feel right now.
You have no idea
what I feel right now.
Harvey: So I'm clear, you're not denying
what we're presenting you with.
You mean that I lied back when
dreibach hired me?
But I'm not some
scam artist either.
I did go to college. I just...
Couldn't afford to graduate.
No one ever questioned it before
because I'm that good
with numbers.
How did they find out
all of a sudden?
They didn't.
This background check
is five years old.
Stan: What?
That doesn't make sense.
- Is this the original?
- Yeah.
So, Tori knew all this time.
This is the same thing
that happened to Paula.
Harvey: Who?
Paula.
Discovered some
undisclosed income.
The books weren't adding up.
She brought it to me.
The next thing I know, she is gone.
I asked Tori about it, then I started
getting shut out of meetings.
They're trying to hide something,
and they're firing me so they can.
Hey. Where are you going?
I'm not signing some agreement.
Are you kidding me?
I'm getting railroaded.
Should I go after him?
No. You've done enough already.
So, you let him leave?
Physically restraining someone
is not in my job description.
What about your associate? The one who
shared the background check.
That was a confidential
internal document.
Stan should have never seen it.
Why did you even have it?
You didn't expect us to fire him without
proof, did you?
Tori's right. Stan shouldn't
have seen it.
Harvey: Then, I'm guilty
of being thorough.
Hey. I still don't understand why you
haven't told us the whole truth.
I mean, if you knew
five years ago,
why did you make it sound like this is
something recent?
Because it only
came to my attention two days ago.
Then who ordered
the background check?
It's routine. You check
with human resources.
Is it routine for
human resources
to keep something from the ceo
for half a decade?
What are you insinuating?
I think what
Harvey is saying is,
given how quickly we tried
to accomplish this,
some of the details
might have gotten lost.
What was also lost is that Stan never
signed the severance package,
which included
the confidentiality agreement.
Which means if he
decides to make waves,
the whole point of
avoiding negative publicity...
Harvey will track down Stan,
and make sure that he signs
the severance package
and the confidentiality
agreement today.
You have my word.
- Thank you.
- Of course.
- I'll be in touch.
- All right, sweetie.
She's lying. She knew about Stan.
She's known for a long time.
And that matters to us why?
Because she's
taking advantage of us.
We are being manipulated
into firing one of her employees
and told not to ask questions.
Well, I have questions.
And the answer, is 10.
As in $10 million per year.
The amount of business
dreibach generates for this firm.
Which means you have to finish
what you started.
Find Stan and get him
to sign those documents.
Oh, and as far as I'm concerned,
that little associate of yours
is to blame for all of this.
That was an honest mistake.
He knowingly revealed a client's
confidential document.
That is not a mistake.
How many more chances are you going
to give that kid?
Oh, I didn't realize
we were keeping score.
But if that's the case, I still think
he's coming out ahead.
Whatever you're doing, stop.
No, you're going to
want to see this.
Paula o'Neil? The former dreibach
employee that Stan mentioned?
She filed a wrongful termination suit
that mysteriously went away.
Really? Let me see that.
Come with me.
Wait. Do you not think
something funny is going on?
You know what?
Here's what I think is going on.
You're sympathizing with Stan
because you think he's you.
That doesn't mean that...
You need to learn something
from what just happened.
Not the least of which is
how anyone,
no matter how valuable,
can be let go.
I can chalk up
what happened with Stan
to youthful exuberance,
but Jessica can't.
So, if you want to work here,
you better go home now,
- because if she sees you...
- Wait, wait. Is she going to fire me?
This habit of you empathizing
with every client,
it's not getting you anywhere.
You want to work in this firm?
You need to deal in facts, evidence,
information that can hold up.
That's what a real lawyer does.
Harvey: Stan.
Did you follow me here?
It doesn't take a sleuth to figure out
that your next step
would be to see another lawyer.
Vople and Williams.
They're a good firm.
Not the friendliest bunch.
If they called you, that is against
lawyer-client privilege.
No one's breaking
any laws, okay?
My assistant has a network
of other assistants
that tell her anything
she wants to know.
Like when someone calls
for an emergency appointment.
You forgot this when you left.
I said I'm not signing anything.
It's nothing to sign.
It's a lawsuit.
You worked for dreibach for nine years.
Oversaw 80 clients.
Filed hundreds of tax returns
and fought 27 audits.
Now, in light of your
recently discovered fraud,
all of that can now
be called into question.
Therefore, you're being sued
for nine years back pay,
plus any expenses incurred
to mitigate the damage you've done.
This is...
This would bankrupt me.
Or you can take what's
behind door number two.
It's aberdeen.
Who?
It's not a who, it's a what.
Dreibach is doing
business with them,
and I think that's
where the problem was.
You don't get it, okay?
I'm only leaving with one of these.
And if it's the lawsuit,
the first thing
your friends upstairs
are going to ask you for
is a big, fat retainer.
And when you tell them that Harvey
specter is the one that's suing you,
you're going to watch the color drain
from their faces.
Now, what would you like to do?
This is not cool. You leave me
in your apartment all night
and say you're going
to be right back.
You don't even thank me
for dropping off your suit.
I had a bad day, Jenny.
So, you couldn't call me.
I almost got fired, okay?
What happened?
It... it's not worth explaining.
Okay. I need to find evidence that our
accounting firm is up to something,
so, I found this woman who filed a
wrongful termination suit against them,
and she referred
me to her lawyer.
Did you call them?
Yeah, but they're this huge firm,
unger and Macy.
They wouldn't take my call.
Why not?
There's a confidentiality clause
in the settlement, for one.
So, it means that
they can't share details like that.
Yeah, I thought all lawyers
secretly shared that stuff.
You're all in
the same club, right?
What? That's not a dumb
thing to assume.
No. No, no, no. That's not dumb at all.
Because...
Unger and Macy have almost as many
Harvard grads as we do, which means...
They're going to be
at the mixer tonight.
And there are two things
that lawyers love to do. Drink and talk.
Man: Hi.
Uh, Mike Ross, class of 2011?
Ross. I'm sorry.
I don't have you on here.
Do you have your ID?
I can run it through the computer.
Uh, my Harvard ID?
What did you say
your name was again?
- Michael Ross, of Pearson hardman.
- Michael Ross...
Boy, you think they ask Harvey
for his ID when he comes to this place?
Harvey specter? You work with
Harvey specter?
Uh, yeah. Yes.
I'm his associate.
I can call him if you like.
Just don't tell him I gave you
any trouble, okay?
Welcome.
Thank you.
Mmm. Oh, god. I'm never going
to survive this.
Deep breaths. You'll be fine.
Jessica: Hey.
I saw the signed severance papers on my
desk. Thank you.
And I also left word for Tori.
Yes, we spoke. She's relieved,
but I wouldn't go so far as to say
completely forgiving.
You ever heard
of aberdeen solutions?
Dreibach listed them
as a consultant firm.
They bill us every month
for their management services.
- Okay...
- What does that mean?
Well, check with accounting.
I did. They can only tell me
how much we pay them.
So, I called aberdeen directly.
It's an automated
answering system.
I left six messages. No returns.
Stan mentioned it. Something just
doesn't feel right.
Are you saying you want to
investigate our client?
They're also our accountants.
And Tori is also a friend.
Harvey, if you
got caught and didn't...
I wouldn't get caught.
I am explicitly telling
you not to do this.
Oh. Then, I'll let you know what I don't
find after I don't look into it.
Hey, should we get the rest of the 2010
grads with us for a pic?
The rest? This is 2011 only.
Isn't he from the 2010 class?
Man: Hey, who is that guy?
No. No, I was 2011.
You're not with us.
Yeah, Rudy. It's Mike.
You know, we...
We hung out a bunch. You...
Where?
Oh, you know what? Maybe I'm thinking
about somebody else.
Sorry about that.
Has anyone seen
that guy here before?
Jenny: Will you excuse me?
Hey. I'm not having any luck.
I wish I could say different, love,
but it's been
a Potter's field for me, too.
What? You get to pretend to be someone
else. I wanted to try. It's fun.
An accent? Hmm.
Okay, I'll stop. What?
You're amazing.
And that's Brian Jennings.
Jenny: Who's Brian Jennings?
I saw his face on unger and Macy's
website today.
What are you waiting for? Go.
Hi.
10 days for public exposure.
Next time you need a bathroom
in Times Square,
go into a hotel.
Five minute recess.
Harvey.
Long time, Anthony.
Morrison: Huh.
You keep company with the high rollers
on centre street.
What are you doing
down in night court?
Need a favor.
What kind of favor?
One that requires access
to sealed court documents.
Can it wait till tomorrow?
I've got this backlog...
When you came to me two years ago in
the middle of the night,
did I tell you it had to wait
till tomorrow?
My chambers.
So... this is quite a surprise.
Who'd ever think that you and I would be
on a double date?
Excuse me?
Oh, come on. You had to notice
when you walked in the room.
She's absolutely gorgeous.
She's completely infatuated with your
girlfriend.
- Come on.
Come on.
I'll introduce you to her.
Charisse, honey. Uh, this is one of my
associates, Mike Ross.
- Oh. So nice to meet you.
- Hi.
And I'm in love with your date.
Seriously. She's just been
telling me about her work with monkeys.
It's fascinating.
- Huh.
- So, really, they're as smart as us?
Oh, smarter.
I never had a chance with him.
I need to use the ladies' room.
Would you excuse me?
Monkeys aren't smarter
than humans. I'm sorry.
Well, it depends on which humans you're
talking about, I guess.
- What?
- Huh?
Morrison:
Name of case and rough date.
Aberdeen v. Paula o'Neil.
Say, six months ago.
Let's see.
Says here that they were listed as
a subsidiary of dreibach
in a wrongful termination suit.
That's it.
That's what I'm looking for.
I can't print this out.
It'll get tagged.
Come around and take a look.
Is that what you were after?
Yeah, that's it.
But what's that?
That links to another
court filing in relation to aberdeen.
Click on it.
Says here that they
filed for dissolution. Earlier today?
The whole company?
That's what it says.
They're officially shut down.
I'm going to need
one more favor.
I think it's great that you found
someone not in law,
who works out in the real world.
Why do you say that?
Because I'm stuck
in a suit all day.
Or an office, or a courtroom.
I think it would be nice to be in
nature. Don't you, Mike?
Well, I love that
you're a lawyer.
In fact,
I'd love to see where
you work sometimes.
You would?
I'm not feeling so well
all of a sudden.
- Yeah.
- Do you think we can go?
- Right now.
- Now.
- Yeah, so great to meet you.
- Lovely to meet you.
- Have a good night.
- Yeah. Bye.
Okay. Why didn't you
do that sooner?
'Cause I had to get this first.
That's the guy, right? From the firm.
That's his employee ID.
He gave this to you?
No, I stole it.
What?
Listen. You can spend all night trying
to get to the guy,
or you could just go
into his firm yourself and look.
- Come on.
- Let's go.
Mike: Yeah, I can barely
keep my eyes open myself.
They got me filing briefs.
Sucks.
You actually came.
You must be Harvey specter.
Joe, was it?
Your friend fill you in on
the deal that's on the table?
Let me just get it straight.
You caught him
rifling through some files
and in lieu of calling
the police, you want me to pay you off?
I never said that. He did.
Oh, that's great. This way,
if I level a charge of extortion,
it's hearsay, huh?
Ten years working for a law firm,
you learn a thing or two.
Which is good, 'cause you sure as hell
don't make a lot of money doing it.
Somehow, I think
you're getting by fine.
Just say I know
the level you guys play at.
Espionage happens all the time,
which is why I know you'll do anything
to protect your secrets.
Well, actually, Joe spina of 2561 clover
Lane in astoria, queens,
I think we all would.
Like those tax returns you filed jointly
for the last six years
while no longer
living with your wife.
You know, the IRS can
destroy you for that.
You think you're the first person to
try to extort me, Joe?
Because that's
the level I play at.
Now, you're a security guard
who likes to take risks.
I like that.
So, here's what
we're going to do.
This here is a generous donation to Joey
junior's little league team.
Now, if it gets to them, it gets to
them. If it doesn't, it doesn't.
But the next time we talk, it's going
to be me who wants a favor.
Officer.
Mike: Do I really need
to pay you back?
Let's start with an explanation.
You said I needed to find evidence.
So, I went to find some.
By breaking into
another law firm?
Is that really worse than paying off
a security guard?
Okay. First of all,
I didn't pay him off.
Second of all, if I hadn't paid him off,
you'd be in jail right now.
You think I might
be right about Stan.
No. I never said you were wrong.
I said we needed evidence.
What? Did you find something?
Dreibach bought a shelf company
13 months ago.
What's a shelf company?
It's a corporation that exists
only on paper
so its owners can
hide their assets.
Isn't that a shell company?
No, it's a shelf company.
Okay. Take a shell company.
Give it a bank account,
credit history, tax returns.
And let it season
for years on a shelf.
Someone buys it,
slots their name into it,
and they walk away with an established
corporation with a pre-existing history.
Anyone looks any closer, you shut it
down and do it again.
That's legal?
Shelf companies are legal. I'm guessing
what Tori's doing with hers isn't.
Wait a minute.
Is it called aberdeen?
Yeah, I saw it on the top of this list
with 37 other management companies,
all related to dreibach, in that
wrongful termination suit.
When we get back to the office,
I want you to find legal precedent that
will allow us to subpoena those records.
Okay. On it.
But do I really have to pay you back?
Every penny.
Wait a minute. How much was
in that envelope?
Mike: Hey. What are you all
doing in my desk?
Dude, you gotta check this out.
Excuse me. Excuse me.
Is that Louis?
Seth: Uh-huh. In the lobby.
Mike: Is this a security camera?
A live feed?
What are you guys doing?
No, this is from last night.
The guys in security
emailed it up
to Louis this morning.
And why are we watching it
on my computer?
Well, we're not going to risk
watching it on one of ours.
And everyone knows your password.
How does everybody
know my password?
Ross 999?
How hard is that to crack?
Okay, 999...
Increases the odds, okay.
Shh. Here it comes.
All: Oh!
What?
Mike: Oh, no.
What did he say to her?
Evidently, Louis wants a restraining
order and he needs this as evidence.
What? Uh... um...
Okay, listen.
Please don't...
I came in here and it... look, I...
Are you okay? Down... Louis.
If the message you left was another
trick to get me down here...
No tricks, I assure you.
Come on in.
Stan, I'm Jessica Pearson.
Oh, yeah. I know who you are.
You said if I accepted the severance
agreement, there wouldn't be a lawsuit.
Well, there is one.
But not against you. With you.
We know about aberdeen. We know what
Tori was orchestrating.
And with your help,
we can expose her.
Why should I help you?
What have you got to lose?
Tell me what you need me to do.
Rachel: Hey.
What does he have you
trying to find this time?
You really want to know?
Uh, I managed to get a look at some
files involving our accounting firm.
What's up with
our accounting firm?
They're stealing from us.
You know your phone bill,
you have all those surcharges?
You have no idea what they mean,
but you pay them, anyway?
Yeah.
Yeah, well, dreibach's doing
the same thing to us,
except all their charges
are a complete scam.
Pretty sure
the phone charges are a scam, too.
Yeah. Maybe.
So, what do you need?
I need a legal reason to get those files
without saying I saw those files.
You need them for court
or you just need them?
Why?
Well, you said you
read them, right?
Yeah.
So, then, you already
have them. In here.
You're right. I do.
Yes. So, you dictate, I'll type.
What? You'd actually
do that for me?
They're stealing from us.
Pearson hardman is my firm, too.
Come on.
Okay.
With the party of the third part
hereto referred to as
Norton llc rendered to...
Not the subject of any litigation
or any claim that
might be reasonably anticipated
to give rise...
Being acknowledged that such appointment
is irrevocable
and shall be deemed
a power coupled with...
Lawfully invested with the power to
make such contracts
or to perform acts
from which it may
be lawfully implied.
That's it. Did we get it?
Saving and... wait for it.
Done.
What?
Your mind. It's just...
It's amazing.
Thanks.
What?
Your mind's amazing, too.
Oh. Thank you. Thank you.
Who are you calling this late?
Oh. She's waiting up for you?
Yeah, I guess you're right.
It's pretty late.
She's probably sleeping by now.
- Yeah.
- I'll just text her.
It's tough to have a relationship
with a first year.
Or any year.
You just don't have a life.
How did you make it work?
Who said I did? It's... it's impossible
to have anything long term
unless you find someone that has the
same 80 hour work week.
And then, that doesn't work either,
because they're busy, too.
Yeah. Well, I'm not going to let that be
the reason that Jenny and I don't...
What are you two
still doing here?
- Uh, it's for Harvey.
- Nothing.
- Uh, but we're done.
- Goodnight.
- Yeah. I'll see you later.
- Bye.
I'm sure you're aware of this, but, um,
I'm just going to remind you, anyway.
Um, this office frowns
upon relationships in the workplace.
Yeah.
- Watch it.
- Oh, god. I'm so sorry.
It's okay.
Hey, uh, thank you
for last night.
The typing.
- Of course. Right.
- Yeah.
- Absolutely.
- It was really helpful.
Mmm-hmm.
Um, hold on one second. Sorry.
Hello?
I said I needed you
in my office.
- And I said I was on my way.
- Save it.
- Those the files?
- Yes. Take them, please.
Stan is in my office. Meet us in
the conference room.
Okay.
Harvey:
Sorry to keep you waiting.
That's okay.
I got your email with the list of
other law firms.
I respect your effort to make amends
by referring new clients.
Harvey: Oh, that wasn't
a list for client referrals.
Those were firms you should consider
for representation.
We're no longer
your attorneys, Tori.
What?
Harvey:
We have no choice, really.
It would be impossible
to represent you
when we plan on suing you
for every penny you've got.
Is this a joke?
Aberdeen solutions. Created in June of
2006, sold to dreibach in 2010,
dissolved two days ago.
Before that,
it was Bolton finances.
And before that,
it was Norton services, Littleton llc...
- Where did you get those?
- We know what you did, Tori.
You couldn't have
subpoenaed these files.
And yet, we have them.
Take a look. They're all there.
And now, we have proof.
Proof of what? Those are all legitimate
corporations used for...
Stealing money and
lining your own pockets.
But don't take my word for it.
Guys?
Hello, Tori.
Harvey: Yeah, we hired Stan
to do a little
independent consulting on our behalf.
And he's come up with
some very interesting connections.
It was easy.
Even if I don't really have a degree.
Jessica: There was that vacation
you invited me on last year,
to your new house
in The Bahamas.
A house you bought
with money you stole from this firm.
My firm.
- Jessica...
- Jessica, what?
Tori: You can't use any of this.
We have
attorney-client privilege.
Harvey: With dreibach
accounting, yes.
With the shelf companies? No.
And unfortunately for you,
you're listed on the shelf companies.
You stole from me.
You either come clean now,
or the only time you'll see your
children in the next decade
will be during
prison visiting hours.
So, I'm going to get
my job back now, right?
I don't see why not.
No, Stan, you're not.
What?
Dreibach's going bankrupt
after this all shakes out.
Even if they don't, they're not going
to hire you back.
Why?
Because you falsified
your resume.
What am I supposed to do now?
Harvey: Well, we just got you more
than your severance package.
I suggest you use it to tide yourself
over until you figure something out.
Stan.
Hey. Your best asset
is your mind.
They can't take that from you.
One little mistake.
You could go back to school,
become legitimate.
Start over?
I never should have done it.
I told you
they wouldn't catch me.
What are you looking for, Harvey?
Positive reinforcement?
Nothing major. A trophy. Nobel.
Would your likeness in bronze
in the lobby be okay?
Bust or life-size?
You did a good thing, Harvey.
But it wasn't just me, you know.
Well, then, I guess
I should give the kid
the benefit of the doubt
from now on.
You should.
Well, you'll be happy to know
that Stan has no idea
what he's going to do
with the rest of his life.
That doesn't make me happy.
What if I tell you I have no idea
what I'm doing with mine?
What the hell are we going to do when
I get caught, Harvey?
- You're not going to get caught.
- That's your answer?
What else is there?
Why?
What?
Hire me. Why would you
do that to me?
- You mean for you.
- No. I don't.
You've made it perfectly clear that you
only do things for yourself.
So, why?
You mean the reason
why I became a lawyer?
Or your friend dealt drugs?
Or you used to cheat?
I cheated because I need to...
You couldn't make money
any other way? Bullshit.
Life is this.
I like this.
That's not me.
Well, if it wasn't me,
you wouldn't be here.
So, if you want this to stop,
all you gotta do is tap out.
- Hello.
- Oh.
You're here to see Mike.
We're going to
celebrate his victory.
Ah.
You know, I actually think
that it's a really,
really good idea that you've come
to pick him up.
In fact, if I were you, I'd do it
a little more often.
Just all those late nights
working with Rachel...
What do you mean?
What do I... oh, come on.
You're a smart girl.
You understand animal behavior.
I think you can figure it out.
Hey. You ready?
Yeah.